{
    "subject": "resource/John_H._Tilelli,_Jr.",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1941-10-02",
    "human_readable": "John H. Tilelli Jr. was born on October 2, 1941.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9431855082511902,
            "question": "When was John H. Tilelli Jr. born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699841499328613,
            "question": "Is October 2nd a significant date for John H. Tilelli Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7590458989143372,
            "question": "What month and day was John H. Tilelli Jr. born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6363832354545593,
            "question": "If John H. Tilelli Jr. was born on a Tuesday, what day of the week would be his birthday in the year 2050?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6149982213973999,
            "question": "What can we infer about John H. Tilelli Jr.'s age based on his birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6139953136444092,
            "question": "How old is John H. Tilelli Jr. as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600855350494385,
            "question": "In what year did John H. Tilelli Jr. come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5241120457649231,
            "question": "How might John H. Tilelli Jr.'s birthdate have influenced his life choices or personality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46038803458213806,
            "question": "Can you imagine what significant events might have happened in the world on October 2, 1941?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.033674463629722595,
            "question": "What are some common traditions or celebrations associated with birthdays?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John H. Tilelli Jr. was born on October 2, 1941.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1031_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you imagine what significant events might have happened in the world on October 2, 1941?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1031_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might John H. Tilelli Jr.'s birthdate have influenced his life choices or personality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1031_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did John H. Tilelli Jr. come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1031_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1031_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple sources that confirm John H. Tilelli Jr.'s birthdate as October 2, 1941."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about John H. Tilelli Jr., including his date of birth as October 2, 1941. Therefore, the statement \"John H. Tilelli Jr. was born on October 2, 1941\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}